You've really learned a lot in this lesson,
你在这节课学到了很多知识
going from approaching unstructured tasks like population segmentation,
从人口细分等无结构任务
to creating features and deploying a k-means clustering model.
到创建特征并部署 k 均值聚类模型
Congratulations. The steps you took to deploy
恭喜部署分割模型所采取的步骤
your segmentation model are steps you can use when approaching any other task.
可以用于任何其他任务
In our industry, often the most challenging step is the first one,
在业内 最难的一步是第一步
figuring out what business question you want to answer.
即决定要回答什么样的商业问题
In this lesson, we gave you an example,
在这节课 我们提供了一个例子
which US counties have similar characteristics,
哪些美国郡县具有相似的特性？
and what kinds of features defined that similarity?
什么样的特征定义了这种相似性？
Not all questions need machine learning to be answered.
并非所有问题都需要用机器学习来解答
But for those that do,
但是对于需要 ML 的问题
you will need to collect and prepare relevant data.
你需要收集和准备相关数据
This step can take quite a lot of time and resources.
这一步可能很耗费时间和资源
It's also good practice to explore this data and see if there's
建议先探索数据
anything notable about the distribution of the data or the different features.
看看数据分布或特征是否有任何明显的特性
Once you have data that is ready to be fed into a model,
获得了可以传入模型的数据后
you need to host that data somewhere.
需要将数据存储在某个位置
You can do this on your laptop by creating a notebook and saving your data locally,
你可以将数据存储到笔记本上 可以创建一个 notebook 并将数据保存到本地
this is useful when exploring a small portion of your data.
这种方法通常适合探索小型数据集
But for large datasets,
但是对于大型数据集来说
you may want to upload those directly into a cloud storage such as Amazon S3.
建议将数据直接上传到云存储平台上 例如 Amazon S3
SageMaker allows you to spin up a notebook instance where you have
在 SageMaker notebook 实例中
the option of uploading and managing large datasets using an S3 bucket.
你可以选择上传大型数据集并用 S3 存储桶管理这些数据集
In this lesson, you work with two different models.
在这节课 你创建了两个不同的模型
You train and deploy a principal component analysis model to simplify population data.
你训练并部署了主成分分析模型来简化人口数据
This technique discards some information into
PCA 可以丢弃原始数据中的某些信息
raw data and create a few meaningful features,
并创建几个有意义的特征
then you use these features to train a k-means clustering model.
然后使用这些特征训练 K 均值聚类模型
After training, you are able to evaluate the model by looking at the modal attributes.
训练模型后 你可以查看模型属性来评估模型
Finally, deployment gave you the ability to assign any data points to a certain cluster,
最后 部署模型后 你可以将任何数据点分配给某个聚类
and you could see which US counties were grouped together,
并看看哪些美国郡县分组到一起
and what kinds of features they shared in common.
它们具有哪些共同的特征
You did all of this from data cleaning to
从数据清理到模型部署
model deployment within a SageMaker notebook instance.
所有这些步骤都可以在 SageMaker notebook 实例中完成
In the next few lessons,
在接下来的几节课
we'll look at more real-world tasks.
我们将查看更多真实任务
You'll be tasked with some supervised learning problems in which you can choose to
你需要解决几个监督式学习问题
use built-in algorithms or custom models of your own.
你可以选择使用内置算法或自定义模型
So I hope you're excited to learn even more.
希望你能期待接下来要学习的知识